# Nadine UWINGABIYE

#### Contact

#### **Address:**

44KK Street, Kigali Kicuro

#### Phone:

+25(0)787939119

#### **Email:**

nadinantire@gmail.com

### Languages

**Kinyarwanda:** Excellent in writing and reading

**English:** very good in writing and reading

### **Summary**

Senior Web Developer specializing in full stack development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML, PHP OOP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLite, Ruby, framework: codelgnitor ,laravel and Rails Strong in system adminstrator, network project management, customer relations and microsoft office 365

# **Skill Highlights**

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused

## **Experience**

Web Developer - 07/2019 to 11/2019 Dive into code, Kigali

- Introduction in Ruby on rails
  - Developed application in Ruby Rails
  - Worked for Dive into code

IT Support - 05/2015 to 07/2019 SPEDAG Interfriet Rwanda, Kigali

- Computer maintenance
- Office system administrator
- Printing and scanning document
- Microsoft office 365 support

#### **Education**

**2017-2019: Advanced diploma in Information Communication Technology, Information Technology option(IT)** at Rwanda Polytechnic IPRC Kigali.

**2013-2015:** A2 certificate in Computer science at ESA BIRAMBO

### **Certifications**

Project analysis and development (certificate) from DataHacher4FI Programming Languages: Ruby on Rails from dive into code,

### References

SHABAN MUHAMMED: IT Manager at SPEDAG **Contact**: 0788848402, **Email**: <a href="mailto:shaban.muhammed@spedaginterfreight.com">shaban.muhammed@spedaginterfreight.com</a>

Engineer BENIMANA Jean Claude: Deputy Principal of Academics and Training at IPRC Kigali. **Contact:** 0781183006